{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Information Assurance & Security (Cybersecurity Fundamentals)",
    "Term": "Prelims",
    "Title": "Prelims Reviewer Pro Max",
    "LastModified": "19 February 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "01 handout 1, 02 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData":  [
    {
      "question": "What is the practice of protecting systems, networks, and programs from digital attacks?",
      "answer": "cybersecurity",
      "choices": [
        "network security",
        "computer security",
        "information security",
        "cybersecurity"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is usually aimed at accessing, changing, or destroying sensitive information; extorting money from users; or interrupting normal business processes?",
      "answer": "cybersecurity",
      "choices": [
        "malware",
        "phishing",
        "social engineering",
        "cybersecurity"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "A successful cybersecurity approach has what kind of protection spread across the computers?",
      "answer": "has multiple layers of protection spread across the computers",
      "choices": [
        "has a single layer of protection spread across the computers",
        "has a single layer of protection spread across the network",
        "has a firewall made of cheese",
        "has multiple layers of protection spread across the computers"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "In an organization, what must all complement one another to create an effective defense from cyber attacks?",
      "answer": "people, processes, and technology",
      "choices": [
        "people, processes, and infrastructure",
        "hardware, software, and network",
        "applications, data, and users",
        "people, processes, and technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Utilizing every type of medium to stay on top of technology and security threats",
      "choices": [
        "Attending conferences and workshops",
        "Sagapin ang world",
        "Conducting vulnerability assessments",
        "Utilizing every type of medium to stay on top of technology and security threats"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Being aware through analyzing and evaluating threats",
      "choices": [
        "Implementing security measures",
        "Monitoring network traffic",
        "Hackin ang wifi nyo",
        "Being aware through analyzing and evaluating threats"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Going through all the systems to check for any potential issue",
      "choices": [
        "Conducting penetration testing",
        "To reach Mythical Glory",
        "Developing security policies",
        "Going through all the systems to check for any potential issue"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Putting proper security measures in place and establishing a protocol",
      "choices": [
        "Training employees on security awareness",
        "Stealing memes",
        "Responding to security incidents",
        "Putting proper security measures in place and establishing a protocol"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Creating reports for shareholders",
      "choices": [
        "Creating reports for employees",
        "Creating reports for customers",
        "Creating reports for management",
        "Creating reports for shareholders"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Spreading the word about security and its importance throughout the company",
      "choices": [
        "Implementing security training programs",
        "Conducting security audits",
        "Enforcing security policies",
        "Spreading the word about security and its importance throughout the company"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is responsible for maintaining the security of a company's computer system?",
      "answer": "Security Architect",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who must think like a hacker would to anticipate their moves and tactics?",
      "answer": "Security Architect",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who sometimes has to work odd hours and must constantly stay updated on the latest developments in security and hacking?",
      "answer": "Security Architect",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "IT experts feel that the best of which profession are former hackers since they are adept at understanding how the hackers operate?",
      "answer": "Security Architect",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who works as an advisor and supervisor for all security measures necessary to protect a company's assets?",
      "answer": "Security Consultant",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who uses their knowledge to assess possible security threats and breaches for prevention?",
      "answer": "Security Consultant",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who creates contingency protocols and plans for when security violations occur?",
      "answer": "Security Consultant",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is an information security expert who systematically attempts to penetrate systems to find vulnerabilities?",
      "answer": "Ethical Hacker",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is also referred to as a white hat hacker?",
      "answer": "Ethical Hacker",
      "choices": [
        "Ethical Kiro",
        "Security Elmer",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief JC"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is responsible for an organization's information and data security?",
      "answer": "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose job is it to learn what day-to-day responsibilities will fall under its umbrella, such as security operations, data loss, program management, and access management?",
      "answer": "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many common cybersecurity career paths are outlined in the handout?",
      "answer": "Four",
      "choices": [
        "Two",
        "Three",
        "Five",
        "Four"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the anatomy of a cyberattack, what is the first step?",
      "answer": "Reconnaissance",
      "choices": [
        "Attack",
        "Expansion",
        "Obfuscation",
        "Reconnaissance"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the anatomy of a cyberattack, what is the second step?",
      "answer": "Attack",
      "choices": [
        "Attack",
        "Expansion",
        "Obfuscation",
        "Reconnaissance"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the anatomy of a cyberattack, what is the third step?",
      "answer": "Expansion",
      "choices": [
        "Attack",
        "Expansion",
        "Obfuscation",
        "Reconnaissance"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the anatomy of a cyberattack, what is the final step?",
      "answer": "Obfuscation",
      "choices": [
        "Attack",
        "Expansion",
        "Obfuscation",
        "Reconnaissance"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What stage of a cyberattack involves researching and gathering information about the target?",
      "answer": "Reconnaissance",
      "choices": [
        "Attack",
        "Expansion",
        "Obfuscation",
        "Reconnaissance"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What stage of a cyberattack involves infiltrating the organization's network?",
      "answer": "Attack",
      "choices": [
        "Attack",
        "Expansion",
        "Obfuscation",
        "Reconnaissance"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What stage of a cyberattack involves intruding all systems on the network using malicious programs?",
      "answer": "Expansion",
      "choices": [
        "Attack",
        "Expansion",
        "Obfuscation",
        "Reconnaissance"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What stage of a cyberattack involves hackers hiding their tracks to mask the origins of the attack?",
      "answer": "Obfuscation",
      "choices": [
        "Attack",
        "Expansion",
        "Obfuscation",
        "Reconnaissance"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many cybersecurity risks are listed that may impact organizations?",
      "answer": "Seven",
      "choices": [
        "Four",
        "Five",
        "Six",
        "Seven"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What has revolutionized the way organizations conduct business today, but also brought vulnerabilities due to its widespread use?",
      "answer": "Technology",
      "choices": [
        "Globalization",
        "Artificial Intelligence",
        "Automation",
        "Technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "From publishing to automotive, industries are facing new, evolving services and business models due to what?",
      "answer": "Technology",
      "choices": [
        "Globalization",
        "Regulation",
        "Competition",
        "Technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What two prevailing trends will heighten cyber risks dramatically?",
      "answer": "Supply Chain",
      "choices": [
        "Economic",
        "Globalization",
        "Technological",
        "Supply Chain"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Companies’ growing reliance on third-party and even fourth-party vendors and service providers presents attackers with new openings into what?",
      "answer": "Supply Chain",
      "choices": [
        "Business Operations",
        "Employee Networks",
        "Internet of Things",
        "Supply Chain"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of devices are everywhere, with each one in a workplace now presenting a potential security risk?",
      "answer": "Internet of Things",
      "choices": [
        "Mobile",
        "Networked",
        "Wireless",
        "Internet of Things"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Many companies don’t securely manage or even inventory all devices of what type, already resulting in breaches?",
      "answer": "Internet of Things",
      "choices": [
        "BYOD",
        "Legacy",
        "Networked",
        "Internet of Things"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Connectivity to the Internet improves what dramatically, but increased connectivity also leads to new security vulnerabilities?",
      "answer": "Business Operations",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Morale",
        "Supply Chains",
        "Regulatory Compliance",
        "Business Operations"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does increased connectivity impact the attack surface, making it easier for attackers to move laterally across an entire network?",
      "answer": "Business Operations",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Productivity",
        "Supply Chain Efficiency",
        "Regulatory Compliance",
        "Business Operations"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who remains one of the most common causes of breaches, yet often doesn't realize the true threat they pose to an entire organization’s cybersecurity?",
      "answer": "Employees",
      "choices": [
        "Hackers",
        "Malicious Insiders",
        "Longanisa Seller",
        "Employees"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "As technology continues to impact every job function, what must organizations establish to mitigate insider risks?",
      "answer": "Employees",
      "choices": [
        "Hackers",
        "Longanisa Seller",
        "Board of Directors",
        "Employees"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is designed to protect and insulate businesses and their customers, but cannot be the sole focus in cybersecurity?",
      "answer": "Regulatory",
      "choices": [
        "Employees",
        "Board of Directors",
        "Business Operations",
        "Regulatory"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Firms must balance both new regulations and evolving cyber threats, which will require vigilance regarding what?",
      "answer": "Regulatory",
      "choices": [
        "Employees",
        "Board of Directors",
        "Business Operations",
        "Regulatory"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose oversight continues to be a point of emphasis, with recent history showing an expanding personal risk for directors and officers?",
      "answer": "Board of Directors",
      "choices": [
        "Technological",
        "Financial",
        "Operational",
        "Board of Directors"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who must expand their focus in cybersecurity and set a strong tone across the company, not only for actions taken after a cyber-incident but also for proactive preparation and planning?",
      "answer": "Board of Directors",
      "choices": [
        "Employees",
        "Management",
        "Faculty",
        "Board of Directors"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of malware specifically aims to extort money by blocking access to files or computer systems?",
      "answer": "Ransomware",
      "choices": [
        "Spyware",
        "Adware",
        "Scareware",
        "Ransomware"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Even after paying the ransom, what type of attack may still result in unrecovered files or systems?",
      "answer": "Ransomware",
      "choices": [
        "Spyware",
        "Adware",
        "Scareware",
        "Ransomware"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What general term refers to any software designed to gain unauthorized access or cause damage to a computer?",
      "answer": "Malware",
      "choices": [
        "Firewall",
        "Antivirus",
        "Anti-malware",
        "Malware"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What deceptive tactic tricks users into revealing sensitive information or making payments?",
      "answer": "Social Engineering",
      "choices": [
        "Encryption",
        "Data Loss Prevention",
        "Vulnerability Scanning",
        "Social Engineering"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of attack often involves clicking on links, downloading malware, or trusting a malicious source due to deception?",
      "answer": "Social Engineering",
      "choices": [
        "Encryption",
        "Data Loss Prevention",
        "Vulnerability Scanning",
        "Social Engineering"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What specific form of attack uses fraudulent emails that mimic reputable sources to steal sensitive data?",
      "answer": "Phishing",
      "choices": [
        "Spamming",
        "Spoofing",
        "Pharming",
        "Phishing"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most prevalent type of cyberattack, often used to steal credit card numbers and login information?",
      "answer": "Phishing",
      "choices": [
        "Spamming",
        "Spoofing",
        "Pharming",
        "Phishing"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are used for encrypting malware to obscure and make the data difficult to detect?",
      "answer": "Crypting Services",
      "choices": [
        "Antivirus Software",
        "Firewalls",
        "Intrusion Detection Systems",
        "Crypting Services"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term defines as buying and selling of malware on the “Dark Web,” a black market for cyber criminals?",
      "answer": "Crimeware",
      "choices": [
        "The Surface Web",
        "The Deep Web",
        "Cloud Storage Platforms",
        "Crimeware"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of software is specifically designed to enable individuals with limited technical skills to commit cybercrimes?",
      "answer": "Crimeware",
      "choices": [
        "Ransomware",
        "Spyware",
        "Adware",
        "Crimeware"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of malware allows hackers to remotely control an infected computer, steal data, or use its camera?",
      "answer": "Remote Administration Tools",
      "choices": [
        "Rootkits",
        "Trojan Horses",
        "Worms",
        "Remote Administration Tools"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What specific type of malware tracks keystrokes to capture confidential conversations and login credentials?",
      "answer": "Keyloggers",
      "choices": [
        "Spyware",
        "Adware",
        "Trojan Horses",
        "Keyloggers"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What works by targeting users who think they are visiting a trusted site but then get redirected to a malicious site?",
      "answer": "Exploit Kits",
      "choices": [
        "Phishing Emails",
        "Malicious Websites",
        "Drive-by Downloads",
        "Exploit Kits"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term refers to stolen data like credit card numbers and login credentials that are often sold on the Dark Web?",
      "answer": "Leaked Data",
      "choices": [
        "Encrypted Data",
        "Anonymized Data",
        "Protected Health Information",
        "Leaked Data"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What devices are physically implanted in POS terminals, ATMs, or gas pumps to steal card data?",
      "answer": "Card Skimmers",
      "choices": [
        "Keyloggers",
        "Spyware",
        "Trojan Horses",
        "Card Skimmers"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What poses a significant security risk due to lack of security patches, often caused by outdated systems?",
      "answer": "Unpatched Systems",
      "choices": [
        "Updated Systems",
        "Legacy Systems",
        "Networked Systems",
        "Unpatched Systems"
      ],
      "reference": "Introduction to Risks, Threats, and Vulnerabilities",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What ensures that sensitive information is accessed only by an authorized person and kept away from those not authorized to possess them?",
      "answer": "Confidentiality",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is implemented using security mechanisms such as usernames, passwords, access control lists, and encryption?",
      "answer": "Confidentiality",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is also common for information to be categorized according to the extent of damage that could be done should it fall into unintended hands?",
      "answer": "Confidentiality",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What ensures that information is true and correct to its original purposes?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle ensures the receiver gets the information the creator intended?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle restricts modification of information to authorized persons only?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What principle aims to keep information in its original state when at rest?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is implemented using security mechanisms like data encryption and hashing?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What might be compromised by non-human-caused events like an electromagnetic pulse?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is important to have in place to ensure data integrity in case of server crashes?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What ensures that information and resources are available to those who need them?",
      "answer": "Availability",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is implemented using methods like hardware maintenance and software patching?",
      "answer": "Availability",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is implemented using methods like network optimization?",
      "answer": "Availability",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What processes are used to mitigate consequences when hardware issues occur?",
      "answer": "Availability",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can be used to guard against downtime and unreachable data due to DDoS attacks?",
      "answer": "Availability",
      "choices": [
        "Integrity",
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What establishes a framework for classifying data based on its sensitivity, value, and criticalness?",
      "answer": "Data Classification Standards",
      "choices": [
        "Data Encryption Methods",
        "Access Control Lists",
        "Data Retention Policies",
        "Data Classification Standards"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first step in the data management life cycle that involves understanding the nature, classification, and location of data?",
      "answer": "Understanding",
      "choices": [
        "Creating",
        "Storing",
        "Using",
        "Understanding"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which phase in the data management life cycle involves activities like collecting data, experimenting, and observing?",
      "answer": "Creating",
      "choices": [
        "Archiving",
        "Destroying",
        "Understanding",
        "Creating"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What stage includes activities such as designing research, locating existing data, and capturing metadata?",
      "answer": "Storing",
      "choices": [
        "Using",
        "Sharing",
        "Archiving",
        "Storing"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which phase involves activities like entering, digitizing, and transcribing data?",
      "answer": "Using",
      "choices": [
        "Creating",
        "Storing",
        "Sharing",
        "Using"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "In what stage would you perform data anonymization, if necessary?",
      "answer": "Using",
      "choices": [
        "Creating",
        "Storing",
        "Sharing",
        "Using"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What stage encompasses activities like distributing, sharing, and promoting data?",
      "answer": "Sharing",
      "choices": [
        "Creating",
        "Storing",
        "Using",
        "Sharing"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which stage includes establishing copyright and controlling access to data?",
      "answer": "Sharing",
      "choices": [
        "Creating",
        "Storing",
        "Using",
        "Sharing"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What stage involves migrating data to the best format and suitable medium?",
      "answer": "Archiving",
      "choices": [
        "Creating",
        "Storing",
        "Using",
        "Archiving"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which stage includes backing up and storing data for long-term preservation?",
      "answer": "Archiving",
      "choices": [
        "Creating",
        "Storing",
        "Using",
        "Archiving"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the final stage of the data lifecycle that involves disposing of data securely?",
      "answer": "Destroying",
      "choices": [
        "Creating",
        "Storing",
        "Using",
        "Destroying"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What stage involves activities like electronic shredding and destroying paper records?",
      "answer": "Destroying",
      "choices": [
        "Creating",
        "Storing",
        "Using",
        "Destroying"
      ],
      "reference": "The CIA Triad and Data Classification Standards",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Employees can create some of the greatest risks to cybersecurity.",
      "answer": "People",
      "choices": [
        "Processes",
        "Technology",
        "Security Audits",
        "People"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "When they are well informed, however, they can also be an asset and the first line of defense.",
      "answer": "People",
      "choices": [
        "Processes",
        "Technology",
        "Security Policies",
        "People"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Often, cybercriminals will specifically target employees as an attack vector based on their lack of knowledge for security practices.",
      "answer": "People",
      "choices": [
        "Processes",
        "Technology",
        "Security Audits",
        "People"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This layer of cybersecurity ensures that IT teams have strategies in place to proactively prevent and to respond quickly and effectively in the event of a cybersecurity incident.",
      "answer": "Processes",
      "choices": [
        "People",
        "Technology",
        "Security Policies",
        "Processes"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "IT security teams should have a cyber-incident response plan in place.",
      "answer": "Processes",
      "choices": [
        "People",
        "Technology",
        "Security Policies",
        "Processes"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "There are hosts of these that security teams can implement to layer their defenses.",
      "answer": "Technology",
      "choices": [
        "People",
        "Processes",
        "Security Audits",
        "Technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This can be especially important when it comes to the Internet of Things (IoT) where the network of connected devices ensures that any device that seeks to be connected has the rights for connectivity to that particular network.",
      "answer": "Hardware authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Cloud technology",
        "Deep learning",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Hardware authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a well-known fact that a majority of data users’ passwords and usernames are weak and makes it easy for hackers to get access to the information systems and compromise sensitive data of a business entity or government agency.",
      "answer": "Hardware authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Cloud technology",
        "Deep learning",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Hardware authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is set to have a significant impact on the transformation of systems security technology.",
      "answer": "Cloud technology",
      "choices": [
        "Hardware Authentication",
        "Deep learning",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Cloud technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "More business enterprises and government agencies have embraced cloud technology to store the vast amounts of information that they generate daily.",
      "answer": "Cloud technology",
      "choices": [
        "Hardware Authentication",
        "Deep learning",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Cloud technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This encompasses some technologies like machine learning and artificial intelligence.",
      "answer": "Deep learning",
      "choices": [
        "Hardware Authentication",
        "Cloud technology",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Deep learning"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "There is a significant deal of interest for systems security in these technologies.",
      "answer": "Deep learning",
      "choices": [
        "Hardware Authentication",
        "Cloud technology",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Deep learning"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many types of Cybersecurity (Security rendered in the network) mentioned in the handout?",
      "answer": "Five",
      "choices": [
        "Two",
        "Three",
        "Four",
        "Five"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This consists of the cyber-physical systems that modern societies rely on.",
      "answer": "Critical Infrastructure Security",
      "choices": [
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Critical Infrastructure Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is more accessible over networks, causing the adoption of security measures during the development phase to be an imperative phase of the project.",
      "answer": "Application Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Application Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This ensures that internal networks are secured by protecting the infrastructure and inhibiting access to it.",
      "answer": "Network Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Network Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a software-based security tool that protects and monitors data in cloud resources.",
      "answer": "Cloud Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cloud providers are constantly creating and implementing new security tools to help enterprise users better secure their data.",
      "answer": "Cloud Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This refers to a wide variety of critical and non-critical cyber-physical systems like appliances, sensors, televisions, Wi-Fi routers, printers, and security cameras.",
      "answer": "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Electricity grid, water purification traffic lights, shopping centers, and hospitals.",
      "answer": "Critical Infrastructure Security",
      "choices": [
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Critical Infrastructure Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Antivirus programs, firewalls, and encryption.",
      "answer": "Application Security",
      "choices": [
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Application Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Extra logins, new passwords, and application security (firewalls, monitored Internet access, antispyware, antivirus)",
      "answer": "Network Security",
      "choices": [
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Software as a Service, Infrastructure as a Service, private, on-site cloud, and virtualization.",
      "answer": "Cloud Security",
      "choices": [
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Cloud Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Connected security systems, thermostats, cars, electronic appliances, and speaker systems.",
      "answer": "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
      "choices": [
        "Cloud Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a set of rules that applies to activities for the computer and communications resources that belong to an organization?",
      "answer": "Security Policy",
      "choices": [
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Security Policy"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should describe how the effectiveness of security measures will be monitored?",
      "answer": "Security Policy",
      "choices": [
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Security Policy"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What ensures that only authorized users can access objects on the system?",
      "answer": "Resource Protection",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Resource Protection"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the ability to secure all types of system resources refer to?",
      "answer": "Resource Protection",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Resource Protection"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the assurance or verification that the resource (human or machine) at the other end of the session really is what it claims to be?",
      "answer": "Authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authorization",
        "Authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which security objective does digital certificates provide a more secure method refers to?",
      "answer": "Authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authorization",
        "Authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an assurance that the person or computer at the other end of the session has permission to carry out the request?",
      "answer": "Authorization",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is performed in context application?",
      "answer": "Authorization",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the assurance that the arriving information is the same as what was sent out?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does understanding integrity require?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is protected from unauthorized changes or tampering?",
      "answer": "Data Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Data Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does data integrity defend against?",
      "answer": "Data Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Data Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What provides consistent and expected results with expected performance?",
      "answer": "System Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "System Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the proof that a transaction occurred, or that a user sent or received a message?",
      "answer": "Nonrepudiation",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Nonrepudiation"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the assurance that sensitive information remains private and is not visible to an eavesdropper?",
      "answer": "Confidentiality",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is critical to total data security?",
      "answer": "Confidentiality",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What monitors security-relevant events to provide a log of both successful and unsuccessful (denied) access?",
      "answer": "Auditing Security Activities",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Auditing Security Activities"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What records tell who is doing what on the systems?",
      "answer": "Successful access",
      "choices": [
        "Unsuccessful access",
        "Graduating access",
        "Access Point",
        "Successful access"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What records tell either that someone is attempting to break the security or that someone is having difficulty accessing the system?",
      "answer": "Unsuccessful access",
      "choices": [
        "Unsuccessful access",
        "Graduating access",
        "Access Point",
        "Successful access"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a federal agency within the United States Department of Commerce?",
      "answer": "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
      "choices": [
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "Security architecture",
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "It's mission is to develop and promote measurement, standards, and technology to enhance productivity, facilitate trade, and improve the quality of life and also establishes IT standards and guidelines for federal agencies?",
      "answer": "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
      "choices": [
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "Security architecture",
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was developed by the International Organization for Standardization?",
      "answer": "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "Security architecture",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can any type or size of organization benefit from?",
      "answer": "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "Security architecture",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a systematic approach to managing sensitive information securely?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO 27000"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes managing risk for people, processes, and IT systems?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO 27000"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is divided into different sub-standards?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes a six-part approach?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO 27000"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is also known as the Information Security Management System [ISMS]?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO 27000"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was initiated to ensure businesses process card payments were secure and to help reduce card fraud?",
      "answer": "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a unified security design that addresses the necessities and potential risks involved in a particular scenario or environment?",
      "answer": "Security architecture",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Security architecture"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What signifies the relationship between the various components inside IT architecture and how they depend on each other?",
      "answer": "Relationships and Dependencies",
      "choices": [
        "Benefits",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Relationships and Dependencies"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is security architecture's main advantage?",
      "answer": "Standardization",
      "choices": [
        "Standardization",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Benefits"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is cost-effective due to the re-use of controls described in the architecture?",
      "answer": "Benefits",
      "choices": [
        "Standardization",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Benefits"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is associated with IT architecture?",
      "answer": "Form",
      "choices": [
        "Benefits",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Relationships and Dependencies"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes a catalog of conventional controls in addition to relationship diagrams and principles?",
      "answer": "Form",
      "choices": [
        "Benefits",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Relationships and Dependencies"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are security controls determined based on?",
      "answer": "Drivers",
      "choices": [
        "Benefits",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Relationships and Dependencies"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What evaluates the business influence of vital business assets and the odds and effects of vulnerabilities and security threats?",
      "answer": "Architecture Risk Assessment",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architecture and Design",
        "Implementation",
        "Operations and Monitoring",
        "Architecture Risk Assessment"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the design and architecture of security services, which facilitate business risk exposure objectives?",
      "answer": "Security Architecture and Design",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architecture and Design",
        "Implementation",
        "Operations and Monitoring",
        "Architecture Risk Assessment"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are security services and processes implemented, operated and controlled?",
      "answer": "Implementation",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architecture and Design",
        "Implementation",
        "Operations and Monitoring",
        "Architecture Risk Assessment"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the day by day processes, such as threat and vulnerability management and threat management?",
      "answer": "Operations and Monitoring",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architecture and Design",
        "Implementation",
        "Operations and Monitoring",
        "Architecture Risk Assessment"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    }
  ]
}